in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can create noise gradients using
如何使用创建噪波渐变
inkscape and the example I'll be
Inkscape和我将成为的例子
applying it to is this eyeball that
把它用在这个眼球上
will'll be recreating so let me open up
将会重现，所以让我敞开心扉
inkscape and we will get started so the
Inkscape和我们将开始这样做
first thing I'm going to do is draw a
我要做的第一件事是画一个
circle so I'm going to grab the circles
圆圈，所以我要抓住圆圈
and ellipses tool and I'm going to hold
和省略号工具，我要拿着
control and shift on the keyboard and
键盘上的Ctrl和Shift键
click and drag to create a circle that
单击并拖动以创建一个圆，该圆
starts from the
从
inside and then I'm going to make this
在里面，然后我要做这个
circle white and then I'll grab my
圈成白色，然后我会拿起我的
selection tool and I will right click
选择工具和我将右键单击
this and go to duplicate and I'll make
把这个拿去复印一下，我来做
this duplicate copy black and I want to
这份复印件是黑色的，我想
apply a radial gradient to this black
将径向渐变应用于此黑色
copy so I'm going to open up the fill
收到，我要打开填充物
and stroke menu if you don't have the
和笔划菜单，如果您没有
fill and stroke menu opened on your
在您的计算机上打开填充和描边菜单
screen you could just click on this
屏幕上你只需点击这个
color stripe down here where it says
这里有彩色条纹，上面写着
fill and it'll open up that menu and
填满，它就会打开菜单，然后
Under The Fill tab I'm going to click on
在填充选项卡下，我将单击
this button right here that says radial
这个按钮在这里，上面写着径向
gradient when you hover your cursor over
将光标悬停在上方时的渐变
it and now I want to reverse this
现在我想要扭转这一点
gradient so that black is on the outside
渐变，因此黑色在外面
and transparency is on the inside so let
透明度是内在的，所以让我们
me grab the gradient tool over here and
我抓住这里的渐变工具，然后
I'm going to click this icon up here in
我要在这里点击这个图标
the tool settings menu that says reverse
工具设置菜单显示为反转
the direction of the
的方向。
gradient and then I'll zoom in on this
渐变，然后我将放大这个
I'm going to double click the path the
我要双击路径
gradient path right here to add a new
在此处添加新的渐变路径
stop and I'm going to bring this out a
停下来，我要把这个拿出来
little bit and then I'll hold control
一点点，然后我就会控制住
and shift and grab this gradient handle
然后按住Shift键并抓住这个渐变控制柄
and just bring this in a little bit like
然后把这个放进去，有点像
that and now I'll zoom out so this is
现在我要缩小了，所以这是
the gradient let me adjust this just a
渐变让我只需调整一次
little more this is the gradient that I
更多的是，这是我的梯度
will be applying the noise gradient to
将噪波渐变应用于
so let me grab my selection tool let me
所以让我拿起我的选择工具让我
move this over a little bit I'm going to
把这个挪过去一点，我要
come up here to where it says filters
到上面写着过滤器的地方来
I'll go to overlays and I will choose
我会去复盖网，我会选择
I'm looking for noise fill from this
我在找这个的噪音填充物
list and I'm going to take this
名单，我要拿着这个
menu I'm going to tick the box down here
菜单我要在下面的方框里打勾
that says live preview and when I do
那就是实时预览，当我这样做的时候
that you can see there is a noise uh
你可以看到有一个噪音呢
filter applied to the gradient there now
滤镜现在应用于那里的渐变
a couple of things to keep in mind first
首先要记住几件事
things first I want to come over here to
我想先来这里看看
where it says noise color and I want to
上面写着噪音颜色，我想
take this a channel and make sure I have
把这个作为一个频道，确保我有
this all the way down to zero if you
一直到零，如果你
don't see an a channel here just come up
在这里看不到一个频道，刚上来
here to this drop down and choose hsl
在此下拉菜单中选择HSL
from this list and now I'm going to come
从这份名单中，现在我要来
back over here to the options Tab and
返回到此处的选项选项卡，然后
the setting that we're going to pay
我们将要支付的设置
attention to the most over here is
这里最受关注的是
dilation we're going to have to adjust
扩张，我们将不得不调整
this dilation slider based on the color
此膨胀滑块基于颜色
that you're working with and how intense
以及你与之合作的紧张程度
you want the uh noise effect to look so
你想让这个噪音效果看起来
if I bring this up you can see it takes
如果我把这件事提出来，你可以看到
away a lot of the effect but if I bring
消除了很多影响，但如果我
it down you could see more of the effect
往下看你可以看到更多的效果
and I'll have to adjust this according
我得把这个调整一下
to my own preferences so for this design
根据我自己的喜好，所以这个设计
I'm going to bring this pretty low right
我要把这个放得很低
about there I think maybe a little
关于那个，我想可能有一点
more and that looks pretty good and once
更多，这看起来很好，而且一次
you have that applied you can click the
您已应用该应用程序，您可以单击
apply button and now the noise gradient
应用按钮，现在是噪波渐变
is applied now if you want to intensify
如果您想要强化
this effect you can apply it a second
这个效果你可以再用一次
time so let me click on live preview
时间到了，让我点击实况预览
again and you can see we can have we
再一次，你可以看到我们可以拥有我们
have a second effect that we're applying
有我们正在应用的第二个效果
there I like how mine looks the first
在那里我喜欢我的第一个看起来
time so I'm just going to deselect this
时间到了，所以我要取消选择此选项
I'm going to close out of this menu and
我要结束这份菜单了
one thing to keep in mind if your
请记住一件事，如果您的
gradient looks a little blurry if the
渐变看起来有点模糊，如果
quality looks kind of low uh it may have
质量看起来有点低，呃，可能有
something to do with the settings so
一些与设置有关的内容
come up here to inkscape preferences I'm
来到这里的Inkscape首选项我是
going to go to inkscape and I'm going to
我要去Inkscape，我要去
click on settings if you're using
如果您正在使用设置，请单击设置
Windows just press control shift p on
Windows只需按下Ctrl Shift p On
the keyboard and in this search bar I'm
键盘，在这个搜索栏里，我
going to type
要去打字了
filter and I'm going to come down here
Filter和我要下来这里
to where it says filter effects quality
到它所说的滤镜影响质量的地方
I have I have best quality set for my
我有一套质量最好的套装
settings here and that gives you the
设置，这为您提供了
sharpest clearest appearance for this
最清晰、最清晰的样子
filter effect that we're applying so if
滤镜效果，所以如果
yours looks a little blurry and soft
你的看起来有点模糊和柔软
it's probably because you have average
这可能是因为你的平均水平
or maybe a lower setting uh so set it to
或者可能设置得更低，呃，所以将其设置为
best quality and close out of the
最好的质量和最好的关闭
menu and now we can grab the gradient
菜单，现在我们可以抓取渐变
tool and we can adjust this like any
工具，我们可以像任何
other gradient you can see we have this
其他的渐变，你可以看到我们有这个
noise effect here that's applied to the
这里的噪波效果应用于
gradient so I'll just adjust this a
渐变，所以我要把这个调整成
little further and now I'm going to
再往前一点，现在我要
create the rest of the eyeball so let me
创建眼球的其余部分，让我
grab my ellipse tool let me deselect
抓取我的椭圆工具，让我取消选择
everything by pressing the Escape key
只需按Esc键即可完成所有操作
and I'm going to snap to the center
我要紧贴中心
Center here and I'm going to hold
中心在这里，我要拿着
control and shift and draw another
Ctrl+Shift并绘制另一个
Circle and I will make this one a
圆圈和我会把这件事变成
lighter shade of blue and then I'll grab
浅一点的蓝色，然后我会抓起
my selection tool right click go to
我的选择工具右键单击转到
duplicate and I'll make this second one
复制一份，我要做第二个
a darker shade of blue and just like I
一种深蓝色，就像我一样
did previously this will be the one that
之前做过的这件事将是
I apply the noise gradient too so let me
我也应用了噪波渐变，所以让我
apply a radial gradient I'll go back to
应用我将返回的径向渐变
my gradient tool I'll reverse the
我的渐变工具，我将反转
direction of the
的方向
gradient and I'm going to zoom in on
渐变和我要放大的
this a little bit I'm going to double
这一点我要加倍
click the path and just adjust this a
点击路径并将其调整为
little bit there we
我们在那里有一点
go and now I'm going to apply that
现在我要把这一点应用到
effect again so let me grab my selection
效果又来了，让我拿起我的选择
tool I will go to
我将转到工具
filters overlays and choose noise fill
滤镜覆盖并选择噪波填充
and I'm going to move my menu over click
我要将我的菜单移动到点击
the live preview button and you can see
实时预览按钮，您可以看到
we have the noise effect there and I'm
我们在那里有噪音效果，我
going to adjust my dilation again just
我要再次调整我的扩张度
so I have the effect that I want now if
所以我现在有我想要的效果，如果
you notice here previously we used a
您会注意到，在此之前我们使用了
lower setting to get that effect for
较低的设置以获得该效果
this color I'm going to use a higher
这个颜色我要用高一点的
setting I'll click apply close out of it
设置我将单击应用关闭它
and now I can go back to my gradient
现在我可以回到我的梯度
tool and adjust this as needed so I'll
工具并根据需要进行调整，这样我就可以
make this oops let me undo that I'm
做这件事，哦，让我解开我
going to adjust this a little
我要稍微调整一下这个
more that's a little closer to the
越多越接近于
effect that I'm going
影响到我要去
for and then I'll press the Escape key
然后我会按Esc键
to deselect everything and I'll grab my
取消选择所有内容，我会抓起我的
circle tool again and create the black
再次使用圆形工具并创建黑色
circle for the center of the eye I'll
以眼睛中心为圆圈，我会
hold control and shift and create
按住Ctrl键并按住Shift键并创建
another Circle and it looks like this
另一个圆圈，它看起来是这样的
one's already black this is actually a
一个已经是黑色的了，这实际上是一个
dark gray I'm going to make this black
深灰色，我要把这个改成黑色
there we go and you can grab your
我们走了，你可以拿起你的
selection tool and you can choose just
选择工具，您可以只选择
how much you want the eyeball to be
你想要的眼球有多大
dilated
扩张的
there and then finally I'm going to
就在那里，最后我要
apply a drop shadow behind everything
在所有东西后面应用投影
here so let me grab my circles and
在这里，让我抓起我的圈子
ellipses tool again snap to the center
椭圆工具再次捕捉到中心
click and drag to draw another
单击并拖动以绘制另一个
Circle I'll make this one black grab the
圆圈，我要把这件弄成黑色，抓住
selection tool and I'm going to lower
选择工具和我要放低
this one to the Bottom by clicking this
点击这个按钮，把这个放到最下面
button up here in the tool settings menu
在工具设置菜单中向上按此按钮
that says lower to the
这意味着更低的
bottom and for this one I'm going to
底部，对于这一次，我将
apply a and blur so I'll come down here
涂上和模糊，这样我就下来了
to the blur slider and I'll bring that
到模糊滑块，我会把它
up like that and now I will apply
就像这样，现在我要申请
another noise overlay to this so let me
另一个噪音覆盖在这上面，所以让我
go to filters overlay and I will choose
转到滤镜覆盖，我会选择
noise fill click live
噪音填充点击实况
preview and again we can adjust this as
预览，再一次我们可以将其调整为
needed and I like how that looks so I I
需要，我喜欢它的样子，所以我
will finalize it by clicking apply close
将通过单击应用关闭来最终确定它
out of the menu and there you go we've
从菜单上走出来，我们就走了
created that eyeball design that uses
创造了那个眼球设计，使用了
noise grading and like I mentioned
噪音分级，就像我提到的
previously these gradients are editable
以前，这些渐变是可编辑的
like any other gradient say for example
例如，与任何其他渐变一样
I wanted to change this from a radial
我想把这个从径向改变
gradient to a linear gradient I could
梯度到线性梯度我可以
just click on the linear button and now
只需点击线性按钮，现在
if I grab my gradient tool you can see I
如果我拿起渐变工具，您可以看到我
have the editable linear gradient like
具有可编辑的线性渐变，例如
that but I liked how it looked
但我喜欢它的样子
previously so I'll put that
之前所以我会把它放在
back and there we go that should do it
回到那里，我们去，应该可以做到
for this tutorial that is how you can
对于本教程，您可以这样做
apply noise gradients to objects using
使用将噪音梯度应用于对象
inkscape if you found this lesson useful
如果您发现本课有用，inkscape
then consider checking out my in inape
然后考虑检查我的inape
master class it's a collection of over
大师班这是一个集合
60 videos where I go over all of the
60个视频，我回顾了所有
tools and features in inkscape and I
inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示
how they work kind of like how I did in
他们的工作方式有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人视频
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提问的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
并随时从我这里获得帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最重要的是没有每月
membership fees you just pay $17 one
会员费只需支付17美元一个
time and you're in for Life I'll have
时间，你将迎来我将拥有的生活
some information about that down below
下面有一些相关信息
if you want to check that out as always
如果您想一如既往地检查一下
thanks for
谢谢你
watching
看
[Music]
[音乐]
h
H